Morevna Project...
Morevna Projectが...
...in association with "Ethic Cinema"...
..."Ethic Cinema"との協賛で...
...presents.
...お送りします
[yawns]
[あくび]
Oh, I fell asleep with the window open again...
また窓を開けたまま寝ちゃったみたい...
Ufff... it's so windy...
うーん...すごい風の音...
...and why can I see Komona through the window?
...それにコモナの街が外に見えるのはどうして？
Komona?!
コモナですって？！
THE CONTEST!!!
あのコンテスト！！！
In previous episodes:
これまでのあらすじ:
Pepper spent a lot of effort...
ペッパーは魔法薬コンテストに向けて...
...preparing for the potion contest.
...とてもがんばっていました
I must've...
きっと...
...must've accidentally fallen asleep...
うっかりして寝ちゃったんだ！
But...
でも...
But...where am I?
でも...ここはどこ？
Oh!!!
あっ！！！
Carrot! It's so cute that you took care of everything!
キャロット！全部面倒を見てくれたのね！
Meow!
にゃあ！
You even thought to bring a potion, my clothes, and my hat!
私の魔法薬に 服に 帽子まで全部用意してくれたんだ！
Well, let's see which potion you brought.
どの薬を持ってきたか確認しないと
So, what do we have here?
ええとこれは...
Whaaaat?!
ええっ？！
Caaaaaaarrrrrooooooot!!!!!!!
キャロッットッ！！！！！！
Pepper & Carrot. Episode 6: The Potion Contest
ペッパー＆キャロット エピソード6 魔法薬コンテスト
As Mayor of Komona, I declare the potion contest...
コモナ市長として ここに魔法薬コンテストの...
...open!
...開催を宣言します！
Four young witches are participating in this contest!
4人の若き魔女がコンテストに参加します！
Please give a huge round of applause!
拍手でお迎えください！
It is an honor to welcome the ravishing and ingenious witch...
偉大なる技術者連合から...
...from the great Technologist's Union!!!..
魅惑の天才を迎えることができ 光栄です！
Coriander!
コリアンダー！
And don't forget about our local girl, Komona's very own witch...
我が街コモナの魔女を忘れるなどありえません...
Saffron!
サフラン！
Our third participant...
3人目の参加者は...
...comes to us from the lands of the setting moons...
...沈む月の土地からやってきました...
...the mysterious...
...謎に満ちた...
...Shichimi!
...シチミ！
And finally our last participant, from the forest of Squirrel's End...
最後の参加者はリスのはずれの森から来た...
...Pepper.
...ペッパーです
Ladies and gentlemen!
さあみなさん！
The winner of the grand prize will be determined by applaud-o-meter!
優勝者は拍手メーターによる投票で決定されます！
Let the games begin!
コンテスト開始です！
[shouting] Well! First up Coriander's demonstration.
[大声]では！最初はコリアンダーの実演です
Ladies & gentlemen...
紳士淑女の皆様...
...fear death no more, thanks to my...
...もう死を恐れる必要はありません この私の...
...Potion of Zombification!
...ゾンビ化の薬があれば！
Amazing!
素晴らしい！
With this mi-ra-cu-lous potion, Coriander defies death itself!
この奇跡的な魔法薬でコリアンダーは死を否定します！
Yes-yes-yes...
あらあらあら...
A potion of Zombification..
ゾンビ化の魔法薬なんて...
that's nothing!
なんでもありませんわ！
It's time to rate MY potion.
今は私の魔法薬をご覧なさい
The real potion you've all been waiting for...
皆様が本当に待ちわびていたのはこちらのほう...
...The Potion of Poshness!
...ゴージャスの魔法薬！
Fantastic!
素晴らしい！
Incredible!
驚異的です！
This potion could make all of Komona rich!
この薬はコモナ全体を裕福にできるでしょう！
It seems,  Coriander has already been eliminated!
コリアンダーの負けはもう確定ね！
Will Shichimi be able to beat that last demonstration?
さてシチミはこの実演に勝つことができるでしょうか？
I... I did not know we had to give a demonstration.
わ...私 実演するなんて知らなかったんです
Come on Shichimi!
さあシチミ！
Everyone's waiting for you!
皆が待ってますよ！
No!..
でも...
I cannot!..
出来ません...
It is too dangerous!..
危険すぎます！
S-sorry!..
ご...ごめんなさい！
Ladies and gentlemen...
紳士淑女の皆様...
...it seems that Shichimi forfeits...
...どうやらシチミは棄権するようです...
Give me that!
およこしなさい！
CAREFUL!!!
気をつけて！！！
What could be so dangerous?
そんなに危険だなんてありえないわ？
You're just scared because your potion isn't as fantastic as mine!
私の魔法薬に負けるのを恐れているだけでしょう？
No-no, it is a potion of...
ち...違いますこの魔法薬は...
...GIANT MONSTERS!!!
...巨大モンスターの薬なんです！！！
Mr. Mayor, Mr. Mayor!
市長さん 市長さん！
Is it my turn now???
私の番かな？
Run!
逃げるんだ！
*МАМАААА*
＊うわああああ＊
You're lucky, Carrot; It seems nobody will see your wondrous potion...
キャロット これってラッキーね だってあなたの魔法薬の正体はバレないかも...
She will destroy our town!!!
街が破壊されてしまう！
Wait,  I think I have an idea!
ちょっとまって 思いついたの！
Hey!
ねえ！
You oversized-posh-zombie-canary!
そこの巨大ゴージャスゾンビカナリアさん！
Wanna try one last "potion"?
最後の魔法薬 試してみたいの？
But first...
でも まず...
...read the label!
...このラベルを見て！
Read it carefully!
しっかりと読んで！
If you don't get out of Komona right away, trust me: I'll pour it all over you!
コモナから今すぐ立ち去らなかったら これをあなたの全身にかけちゃうから！
Understood?!
わかった？！
Because she saved our town we award first place to...
街を救ったので優勝は...
...Miss Pepper!
ペッパーです！
For her wonderful potion!
素晴らしい魔法薬ですね！
Huh, in fact...
あはは ええと...
...it's not really a potion...
実は これは 魔法薬じゃないんです
...it's just my cat's pee sample from his last trip to the vet!
この前獣医に行った時の 私の猫の尿の試料なんです！
Isn't it, Carrot?
でしょ キャロット？
Meow!
にゃお！